<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aman Aniket</title>
    <link>https://amananiket.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Aman Aniket</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 14:02:37 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://amananiket.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I am a Liberal</title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/posts/i-am-a-liberal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 00:12:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/posts/i-am-a-liberal/</guid>
      <description>Yeah, I&amp;rsquo;m a liberal. I&amp;rsquo;m a nationalist and by association of the republic of India being a liberal democracy, I become a liberal. But wait, I was born a Hindu and India being a admittedly secular country, I inherited the religion.
 I&amp;rsquo;m many more nouns if I keep on thinking about it which raises the question, what indeed is religion? Why do we unquestionably follow a religion? Some of us have no second thoughts about how the creation of the universe played out owing to our dogmas derived from religious texts, but a lot of others indeed have a part of us questioning constantly about the gaps in our understanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Religion</title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/posts/religion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 16:04:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/posts/religion/</guid>
      <description>All of us are born into a religion. A lot of us spend our whole lives defending a dogma that was associated to us just by a matter of consequence. Come to think of it, I had myself not tried seeing the bigger picture and had largely procrastinated investigating the central idea of religion. The question was posed while going through Sapiens which is a de-facto outer view of the history of human existence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book review: Thinking, Fast And Slow</title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/posts/thinking-fast-and-slow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 15:33:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/posts/thinking-fast-and-slow/</guid>
      <description>Daniel Kahneman, the author of Thinking, Fast and Slow is a renowned psychologist and a Nobel laureate in Economics. Through this book, he talks about his broader contribution to behavioral psychology and the science of decision-making including this Nobel winning work Prospect Theory.
 During the course of our day-to-day functioning, we take innumerous decisions. A majority of these decisions come naturally to us guided by our intuition, often at the risk of fleeting assumptions and systematic errors in judgement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Racing</title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/posts/racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 00:32:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/posts/racing/</guid>
      <description>I have never been a racing person. What I have always enjoyed and found challenging though is the ultra aspect of things. Having said that, there&amp;rsquo;s that thrill you get from speed which is all but a different flavor of the sport. So when The Champions Sportive was announced, which essentially is planned to be a set of 102K competitive races across 8 cities of the country. This is the first edition and Bangalore was the first city to host it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mysore</title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/posts/mysore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 01:26:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/posts/mysore/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I started attempting long distances on the cycle which was roughly at the beginning of 2017, I have always looked for out-and-back destinations which
 Have a healthy amount of climb. Approachable mileage given my current conditioning.  Given my last outing was an around 200k affair, I wanted to really try myself out this time. The last one had been to the Avalabetta peak in the mid-April scorching heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being an endurance athlete</title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/posts/being-an-endurance-athlete/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 07:05:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/posts/being-an-endurance-athlete/</guid>
      <description>I am asked by my mother, “Why do you cycle so much? Planning to go to the US to meet your brother?”. She already thinks bigger than me.
 Being one? Guess what, I didn’t decide to be one, one fine day. It just came to me in the form of the beautiful sport of Running. I started running because I had lost touch with any form of activity. I was in sophomore year of college, and running seemed liked the best way to start embarrassing myself lesser when on a weighing scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uno</title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/posts/uno/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 00:06:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/posts/uno/</guid>
      <description>I had always wanted to host my own blog. I guess I was just too lazy to actually write one from scratch. But what you see is indeed a work conceived and built bottom-up and not a clone. I&amp;rsquo;m proud of myself that I could come around convincing myself that I should do this. For the interested reader, this website is built on the Hugo framework with Cactus theme. Building yourself one like this is pretty easy and should be a matter of minutes if you know your way around code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For the love of cycling</title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/posts/for-the-love-of-cycling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 16:20:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/posts/for-the-love-of-cycling/</guid>
      <description>The sport of cycling came and stuck to me quite serendipitously putting me on the right track in a lot of aspects.
 I still remember the first time I decided I wanted to get a cycle. Things came up to a point where I would not budge or eat anything without getting one. My parents had to give in quickly as they rarely saw this quiet and reserved kid really adamant about something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I wrote a poem!</title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/posts/poem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 16:33:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/posts/poem/</guid>
      <description>Yes, had to be done. This came up to me during one of the discussions that I should write a poem. As impulsive as I am, I went ahead and actually wrote one. Please pardon me for wasting 2–3 minutes of your life (depending on your wpm of course)
 What would I want from the girl whom I’d want to be with?
I would say just be yourself. Just follow your heart,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conquering Avalabetta and more...</title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/posts/conquering-avalabetta-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 16:11:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/posts/conquering-avalabetta-and-more/</guid>
      <description>Avalabetta is a beautiful hilltop located around 100 kms from Bangalore. It is an ideal place for a short trip with great scenery to offer.
 The mountain biking bug first bit me after incidentally joining a YHAI 7 day trip to Jalori Pass. Nearly a year later, I was about to attempt cycling around 200 kms in a day. I had been cycling around 25–30 kms a day for 6 months now so I knew I had the conditioning, but a long stretch of cycling brings a handful of challenges with it, the intense 35 degrees arid weather topping the list for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, Goodbye</title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/posts/hello-goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 15:28:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/posts/hello-goodbye/</guid>
      <description>Somebody asks me, ‘Oh, You are a final year right? You must be feeling terrible about leaving this place! “. Should I? I think. And then indulge myself into a reverie
 I came to to this place exactly 5 years ago with lots of hopes and expectations. The excitement of entering that phase of life is inexplicable. The most dominant feeling coming here was freedom. Yes, more than anything else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/jabwemet/photo/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/jabwemet/photo/1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/jabwemet/photo/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/jabwemet/photo/2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/jabwemet/photo/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/jabwemet/photo/3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/jabwemet/photo/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/jabwemet/photo/4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/jabwemet/photo/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/jabwemet/photo/5/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/jabwemet/photo/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/jabwemet/photo/6/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/jabwemet/photo/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/jabwemet/photo/7/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jab We Met</title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/jabwemet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/jabwemet/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>