<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>musings on Aman Aniket</title>
    <link>https://amananiket.com/categories/musings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in musings on Aman Aniket</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 16:04:46 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://amananiket.com/categories/musings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Religion</title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/posts/religion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 16:04:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/posts/religion/</guid>
      <description>All of us are born into a religion. A lot of us spend our whole lives defending a dogma that was associated to us just by a matter of consequence. Come to think of it, I had myself not tried seeing the bigger picture and had largely procrastinated investigating the central idea of religion. The question was posed while going through Sapiens which is a de-facto outer view of the history of human existence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For the love of cycling</title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/posts/for-the-love-of-cycling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 16:20:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/posts/for-the-love-of-cycling/</guid>
      <description>The sport of cycling came and stuck to me quite serendipitously putting me on the right track in a lot of aspects.
 I still remember the first time I decided I wanted to get a cycle. Things came up to a point where I would not budge or eat anything without getting one. My parents had to give in quickly as they rarely saw this quiet and reserved kid really adamant about something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I wrote a poem!</title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/posts/poem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 16:33:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/posts/poem/</guid>
      <description>Yes, had to be done. This came up to me during one of the discussions that I should write a poem. As impulsive as I am, I went ahead and actually wrote one. Please pardon me for wasting 2–3 minutes of your life (depending on your wpm of course)
 What would I want from the girl whom I’d want to be with?
I would say just be yourself. Just follow your heart,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, Goodbye</title>
      <link>https://amananiket.com/posts/hello-goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 15:28:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amananiket.com/posts/hello-goodbye/</guid>
      <description>Somebody asks me, ‘Oh, You are a final year right? You must be feeling terrible about leaving this place! “. Should I? I think. And then indulge myself into a reverie
 I came to to this place exactly 5 years ago with lots of hopes and expectations. The excitement of entering that phase of life is inexplicable. The most dominant feeling coming here was freedom. Yes, more than anything else.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>